

# VUONG HUYNH THANH TUAN

Mobile Developer(Flutter)

- November 5
- Male
- 0969150217
- ttuanvuong26@gmail.com
- ← HCM City,VietNam
- https://www.facebook.com/ttuan2

# **OBJECTIVES**

I'm a Flutter Developer with more than 3 years of experience developing and maintaining lots of applications using Flutter. I have worked with outsourcing and product companies. Ability to read documentation, write docs and communication skills. I can read and communicate in English .I'm looking for a company that can help me grows as a developer, in knowledge and my English.

# SKILLS

- XCode
- Clean Architecture ,OOP
- GetX, Provider,Stream ,
  Stateful Stateless async await

# **PROJECT EXPERIENCE**

Nov 2022 - Present

### FLUTTER DEVELOPER | Ecommerce App

- Apply Flutter Framework for old application base on native(Kotlin,Swift)
- Work with BE team create many feature for the new app: Order listing, Add product to cart, purchasing product, connect with momo for purchasing,
- Apply many technology into app fo handle the app: CI/CD auto build into store, intergrate module app for easier management, auto generate image, Add app in app, apply GA4 to track customer action, FCM for push notify for customer.
- · Work with design team to create lots of screen.
- · Connected with momo, vn pay wallet.
- · Work with Melos to manage many modules clearly and easily
- Work with get\_it, json\_serializable, retrofit, floor\_generator to auto generatate classes for manage the sources more professionally and quickly
- Build localization, interceptor, local themes and lots of things are related to technical core
- · Team size: 4

Nov 2022 - Present

### FLUTTER DEVELOPER | MINI APP

- Mini apps is a lot of app Flutter add in another native app
- Work with method channel to communication between Flutter and Native app
- Features are Clinic Finder, Watch Live Stream, Magazine, ...
- Live stream mini application is using a realtime database to play a live from the sales department for make it easier for consumer to buy products.
- Find nearby stores, clinics mini application is using a google maps sdk to find a spectific stores and clinics for consumer to easily get in there
- Call ,chat mini applycation is using Omi Sdk to intergation features for consumer to call, chat with a call center if they have any problem and want to complaint for us.
- Team size: 5
- CHplay: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.concung.ecapp

Jan 2022 - Present

# FLUTTER DEVELOPER | POS APP

- An Sales management internal application serves for sale in stoes
- Dev new features with requests from many departments in the company
- Get complaints and fix them immediately
- Design mini games for customer to get presents such as Lucky Wheel, Flip Card Get Presents, ...
- Apply mutiple flow to purchase goods for application
- · Maintaning App
- Team size: 2

D-- 0001 I...- 0000

σιαισται,σιαισισσο, ασγιίο αγγαίτ,

#### MQTT

- Connect with Nodered
- Unit test
- SQLite ,HTTP, Firebase
- Nullsafety
- · Work with Backend
- · Comunicate with native app
- Experience in working with Git, Jira

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

#### 2022

• TOEIC 700

#### 2021

 Degree in information technology engineering

# **HONORS & AWARDS**

#### 2019-2020

-Twice to receive scholarships to encourage study

# FLUTTER DEVELOPER | MOON&SHEEP

Dec 2021 - June 2022

- Moon & Sheep is a sleep music application that includes outstanding features such as: Thai Taoism, Stories, Lullabies, White Sounds, Music without lyrics...
   especially suitable for pregnant mothers and children under 3 years old.
- · Developing new features, maintaining app, fix bug
- Team size: 4
- CHplay: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=concung.com.ccapp.moonsheep

Jun 2022 - Present

#### FLUTTER DEVELOPER | TASTEE POS

- · An Sales management software developed for the seller community
- Manage orders right on your phone Create online or offline sold orders right on your phone easily
- · Manage sales history, easily check orders
- Sales report of best selling items and times
- · Print receipt with bluetooth, network printer
- Firebase cloud messaging receive notify when order success
- Support team leader to upload applications into the stores.
- Team size: 2
- CHplay: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=com.tastee.pos&hl=vi&gl=US

Jun 2022 - Feb 2021

#### LEADER FLUTTER DEVELOPER | NUTIFOOD APP

- A online selling app writter in Flutter.
- Works with BE team and assigns tasks for member in the team, supports team for build the core.
- Works with customers,testers to get requests and issues .Finally, find the way to resolve the problem as soon as possible
- · Transfer with Momo, Zalo pay, Shoppee pay, Master Card,
- · Work with dynamic link, deeplink
- Cart management
- Apply Firebase cloud messaging to get notifies for end users.
- Team size: 3

Mar 2021 - Dec 2021

# FLUTTER DEVELOPER | TNEX

- · An e-wallet application of MSB Bank writter in flutter .
- Get the request from customer to develop new features , maintaining app ,fix bug
- Upgrade app to new version flutter 2.0
- Develops games for customer to get presents, give a quest for customer to get impressive discounts
- Team size : 2

 https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=vn.tnex.consumer&hl=vi&gl=US

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

December 2021 - Present

**CON CUNG JOIN STOCK COMPANY** | Fulltime

Flutter Developer

January 2021 - November 2021

SUGA GROUP | Fulltime

Flutter Developer

January 2021 - February 2022

TIEN PHONG | Freelancer

Flutter Developer

September 2020 - December 2020

IECS | Intern Flutter Developer

# **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2021

INDUSTRIAL UNIVERSITY OF HO CHI MINH CITY | Major: Information

Technology

